

TOBIAS MAFFIA

WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer May 2022 - Ongoing | ITBA HTML, CSS, Js, Python, SQL, Django, Git, Github.

Full Stack Web Developer May - dic 2021 | Digital House NodeJS, Js, SQL, Jquery

UX/UI Designer
Jun - oct 2021 | Coderhouse

Design Thinking, UCD, Adobe XD, Wireframing Research, Prototyping, etc.

Bachelor Degree in Economics 2019 - 2021 | UADE

25/40 approved grades.

Bilingual High School 2013 - 2017 | Sarmiento International School

Advanced English (exchange program)
2016 Eckerd College, St. Petersburg, U.S

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, SQL, Python.
AdobeXD, Photoshop and Figma.
Spanish as my mother language,
Fluent in english.
Intermediate Portuguese.
Leadership and teamwork.
Empathy and customer oriented.
Great communication skills.

CONTACT

+ 54 9 1159134960 maffiatobias@gmail.com LinkedIn: Tobias Maffia

Portfolio: https://tmaffiastudio.netlify.app/

Buenos Aires - Argentina

ABOUT ME

I'm passionate about technology and innovation; I believe that we are in the midst of a digital and cultural transformation, in which empathetic and user-oriented people are needed to make this change a much more human and pleasant experience. Today I seek to be part of this transformation by improving the experience of digital users.

I developed my career both in Fintech and in traditional banking, always in positions related to user experience, and currently in web design and development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Banco Ciudad (sep 2021 - ongoing) Jr Developer

- Help with the design and development of software.
- Write clean code, mainly for the front-end.
- Design user interfaces.
- Test and debug softwares to keep them optimized.

Banco Ciudad (noviembre 2019 - septiembre 2021) Banker

- Knowledge of all the products and services offered by the bank
- Collect and gather information from both new and existing clients to analyze and build reports.
- Resolving clients issues and perform administrative tasks.
- Credit analysis due authorizing and evaluating overdrafts and loans.

Mercado Libre (july 2018 - nov 2019) Customer Experience analyst

- Provide support to the marketplace users.
- Analyze CX metrics such as NPS, Contact Rate and others.
- Give support to other areas such as Communication, Processes and UX/UI designers.